Music
Here we go again this year, Live Meets Live!
Thank you very much for inviting me to perform. I will be performing under my real name.
It's been a while since I've performed solo.
I often perform my songs through Live Meets, so this is my second time performing.
I'm going to rehearse after this.
I'm going to have rehearsal after this and perform at night, so I'd like to spend a little time relaxing.
Fast forward
Sound check is in progress.
We're checking the keyboard.
Boo Bar, a stylish bar
Hey, this time we're doing a little lab work, so we're going to check out the thinness...
A lot of them are like beakers...
They have beakers like this...
Buy a change of clothes inside.
Now it's time for rehearsal.
We're doing a lot of different things right now.
Guitar.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
Please do this once.
Yes.
To put words to justice and so on.
It's getting boring.
Unknowable hope
Today the song gets rougher and rougher
What if it's a broken hand
Sweat you can't see
Drink your eyes out
Say it out
If I don't let it go
The same path as yours
It's still overflowing
How can I be so honest with you?
Because I can't be honest Because I can't be honest with you.
No matter how many times we meet
The first time I hear your voice
What kind of
If it's me
Look up at the sky
I'd be lost
I can't hold on to it
I'm sure
I want to deliver it
It's my time
Tonight, too
I long for you
Tonight
Stay
Oh yeah
Good night
So today, I'm Takashi Matsuo, aka Takashi Matsuo, aka ssn, aka solo artist, performing at a live event called "Live Meets.
I'm performing under my solo name, Takashi Matsuo ssn. I'm sorry to say it's just before the show, but it's almost my turn.
This is my second time performing at this event, so I'm really happy to be here.
I'll do my best.
I'm wearing a British-style jacket.
And on top of it, for the show...
I'm thinking that I'd like to wear a khaki coat on top of this for the main event.
Makeup is done, and it looks like this.
Haruha-san is performing right now.
After the next two groups are finished...
It's my turn.
I'll do my best.
But first, I'll be collaborating with Yasumoto-san.
We'll be collaborating on a song for Cho-Watch.
I'm looking forward to that too.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
Well...
I'd like to say that I'm a friend of yours.
Today... Today.
Same here.
I think a lot of my friends are out there.
I think my SDR friends are out there.
You know...
There's one person who's been very kind to me.
I have an older brother.
I'd like to introduce him.
I'd like to invite him as a special guest.
I'd like to invite him.
I think so.
Let's have him come this way.
I'm Takamori Matsuo.
I'm Takamori Matsuo, a superhero, and this is Yasumoto-san's last song.
I'll be performing after this.
I'm a bit of a skin supervisor, but...
But I've got the impression that everyone will welcome me warmly.
I'll do my best to make you enjoy the show.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
We're in the middle of a changeover.
It's great to see all the artists.
They've been warming up to us.
We're going to try to have a good last show.
I mean, let's have fun.
Let's have fun!
The lights are burning like they're backstage.
He's lighting up the stage.
Our ever-ambitious stylist...
He's on his cell phone.
He's got the lights on.
Thank you so much.
I am her puppy and I could save her days.
I love her.
I love her too.
She's down in her ribs.
She loves her. She loves her.
I have improved her лет raw.
I love her.
This feeling that it could start anytime. It's so good.
I love Vietnam, especially when you start with the attack video.
When to enter, when to enter, you know?
When to start with an overture....
It depends on the person.
You guys are so good!
Remember?
You forgot?
Thank you!
Thank you very much for your hard work. Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you very much.
Live Meets finished, this is Dayaka Yasuno.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for letting us collaborate with you on the song "Arcind of Love" by Super Express.
I was really happy when you said you wanted to collaborate with us.
I was so happy to hear you say such a thing.
I asked you to do this in the midst of your busy schedule.
I am so grateful for your kindness.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much. I'm so happy.
I've wanted to sing with you for a long time.
I'm so happy.
I was so happy.
I was very happy, too, and I was also very happy about the live performance, DJ.
Yes.
I thought I was being played.
I tried.
I tried it, and it was like I was dancing.
The live performance was really good.
No, no, no, but what would you do if I said that? The live show was great, wasn't it?
I am happy. I'm so happy.
You really have a wonderful singing voice.
Thank you very much. I've seen so many collaborations and various artists perform at the live MEETS.
I wonder if they will do it again next time.
I wonder how many times.I wonder how many times.
I want to get out.
I'd like to get out.
I'm looking forward to working with you. Confirmation of the parties involved.
Thank you very much.
Delicious.
I had it from one time.